statusbrew.com 2019-12-25

# Privacy Policy

Chiax LLC (Statusbrew) provides this Privacy Policy to inform you of our policies and procedures regarding the collection, use, protection, and disclosure of Personal Information received from your use of this website, located at [https://statusbrew.com](https://statusbrew.com/) (“Site”), as well as all related applications, browser extensions, and other services provided by us (collectively, together with the Site, our “Service”), and in connection with our customer, vendor, and partner relationships. This Privacy Policy also tells you about your rights and choices with respect to your Personal Information, and how you can reach us to update your contact information or get answers to questions you may have about our privacy practices.

Registration with, use of, and access to the Service is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use located at <https://statusbrew.com/tos>. All terms not defined in this Privacy Policy will have the meanings set forth in the Statusbrew Terms of Use.

#### 1\. PERSONAL INFORMATION WE MAY COLLECT

For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, “Personal Information” means any information relating to an identified or identifiable individual. We obtain Personal Information relating to you from various sources described below.

Where applicable, we indicate whether and why you must provide us with your Personal Information, as well as the consequences of failing to do so. If you do not provide Personal Information when requested, you may not be able to benefit from our Service if that information is necessary to provide you with the service or if we are legally required to collect it.

#### 2\. PERSONAL INFORMATION PROVIDED BY YOU

**Registration.** If you desire to have access to certain restricted sections of the Site or request to receive marketing materials, you may be required to become a registered user, and to submit the following types of Personal Information to Statusbrew: your name, email address, phone number, full username, password, city, and time zone.

**Customer Support.** We may collect information through your communications with our customer support team or other communications that you may send us and their contents.

**Making a Purchase.** When you make payments through the Service, you will need to provide Personal Information such as your credit card number and billing address.

**Social Media.** In order to allow you to post to your social media platforms, we may ask you to provide your username, account ids, social handle, timezones, and email address.

**Other.** We may also collect your contact details when you provide them in the context of our customer, vendor, and partner relationships.

If you connect your third party social media account to your Statusbrew account, we may collect certain information stored in your social media account such as:

  * **Facebook:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect a Facebook page or profile to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from Facebook regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username/page ID or profile ID, access tokens, sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

  * **Twitter:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect a Twitter profile to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from Twitter regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username/profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, retweets, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

  * **Instagram:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect an Instagram profile to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from Instagram regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username/profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

  * **LinkedIn:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect a LinkedIn profile to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from LinkedIn regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username/profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

  * **Google My Business:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect a Google My Business page to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from Google regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

  * **Youtube:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect a Youtube profile to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from Youtube regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and published videos. This includes the content of your videos and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

  * **Pinterest:** Statusbrew may allow you to connect a Pinterest page to your Statusbrew account, in which case we will access certain information from Pinterest regarding your account. In particular, we may collect profile image, display name, username / profile ID, access tokens, and sent posts. This includes the content of your post and engagement data (such as click rates, likes, re-shares, impressions, as well as general engagement counts), to the extent permitted by applicable law. This data will only be used by Statusbrew to provide you with the Service you expect and will not be shared with any third parties.

Additionally, if you connect **Twitter** , **Facebook** , **LinkedIn** , **Google My Business, Youtube** or **Instagram** when utilizing **Statusbrew Engage** we may collect profile image, display name, username/page ID, access tokens, sent or received comment text and sent or received private message text.

Additionally, if you connect **Twitter** , **Facebook** , **Pinterest** , **LinkedIn** , **Google My Business, Youtube** or **Instagram** when utilizing **Statusbrew Reports** we may collect profile image, display name, username/handle, access tokens, social account's insights data, demographic data, video insights, sent tweets, social account’s followers count, and social account’s audience data.

##### 2b. Personal Information Automatically Obtained from Your Interactions with the Service

**Log Data.** When you use our Service, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website (“Log Data”). This Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type or the domain from which you are visiting, the web-pages you visit, the search terms you use, and any advertisements on which you click.

**Cookies and Similar Technologies.** Like many websites, we also use “cookie” technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve the Site and our Service. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your computer’s hard disk. A session cookie enables certain features of the Site and our service and is deleted from your computer when you disconnect from or leave the Site. A persistent cookie remains after you close your browser and may be used by your browser on subsequent visits to the Site. Persistent cookies can be removed by following your web browser help file directions. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. Statusbrew may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with the Site and our Service, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on the Site, and to improve the Site and our Service. We may also automatically record certain information from your device by using various types of technology, including “clear gifs” or “web beacons.” This automatically collected information may include your IP address or other device address or ID, web browser and/or device type, the web pages or sites that you visit just before or just after you use the Service, the pages or other content you view or otherwise interact with on the Service, and the dates and times that you visit, access, or use the Service. We also may use these technologies to collect information regarding your interaction with email messages, such as whether you opened, clicked on, or forwarded a message, to the extent permitted under applicable law. You can instruct your browser, by editing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. Please note that if you delete, or choose not to accept, cookies from the Service, you may not be able to utilize the features of the Service to their fullest potential.

#### Do Not Track

Statusbrew does not process or respond to web browsers’ “do not track” signals or other similar transmissions that indicate a request to disable online tracking of users who use our Service. **Third Party Web Beacons and Third Party Buttons** We may display third-party content on the Service, including third-party advertising. Third-party content may use cookies, web beacons, or other mechanisms for obtaining data in connection with your viewing of the third party content on the Service. Additionally, we may implement third party buttons, such as Facebook “share” buttons, that may function as web beacons even when you do not interact with the button. Information collected through third-party web beacons and buttons is collected directly by these third parties, not by Statusbrew. Please consult such third party’s data collection, use, and disclosure policies for more information. **Links to Other Websites** Our Site contains links to other websites. The fact that we link to a website is not an endorsement, authorization or representation of our affiliation with that third party. We do not exercise control over third party websites. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit Personal Information from you. Other sites follow different rules regarding the use or disclosure of the Personal Information you submit to them. We are not responsible for the content, privacy and security practices, and policies of third-party sites or services to which links or access are provided through the Service. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

#### 3\. HOW WE MAY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We may use the Personal Information we obtain about you to:

  * create and manage your account, provide our Service, process payments, and respond to your inquiries;
  * manage account authentication such as two-factor authentication
  * communicate with you to verify your account and for informational and operational purposes, such as account management, customer service, or system maintenance, including by periodically emailing you service-related announcements;
  * tailor our Service (e.g., we may use cookies and similar technologies to remember your preferences);
  * publish your content, comments or messages on social media platforms;
  * provide tailored advertising, for Statusbrew services, via Google AdWords;
  * aggregate your Personal Information for analytical purposes;
  * provide customer support;
  * operate, evaluate and improve our business (including by developing new products and services; managing our communications; determining the effectiveness of our advertising; analyzing how the Service is being accessed and used; tracking performance of the Service; debugging the Service; facilitating the use of our Service);
  * send you marketing communications about products, services, offers, programs and promotions of Statusbrew, and affiliated companies;
  * ensure the security of our Service;
  * manage our customer, service provider and partner relationships;
  * enforce our agreements related to our Service and our other legal rights; and
  * comply with applicable legal requirements, industry standards and our policies.

If you are located in the European Economic Area, we may process your Personal Information for the above purposes when:

  * you have consented to the use of your Personal Information, For example, we may seek to obtain your consent for our uses of cookies or similar technologies, or to send you marketing communications.
  * we need your Personal Information to provide you with services and products requested by you, or to respond to your inquiries,
  * we have a legal obligation to use your Personal Information, or
  * we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information. In particular, we have a legitimate interest in using your Personal Information to ensure and improve the safety, security and performance of our Service, to anonymize Personal Information and carry out data analyses.

We may disclose the Personal Information we collect about you as described below or otherwise disclosed to you at the time the data is collected, including with: **Social Media Platforms** Our primary purpose for using information is to publish your content on social platforms, allow you to track metrics for analytical purposes, and engage with customers through public replies and conversations (direct messages or “DMs”). We may allow you to link your account on Statusbrew with an account on a third party social network platform, such as Twitter or Facebook, and to transfer your information to and from the applicable third party platform. Once you share your content to a social media platform, its use will be governed by that platform’s privacy policy. **Service Providers** We engage certain trusted third parties to perform functions and provide services to us, including hosting and maintenance, error monitoring, debugging, performance monitoring, billing, customer relationship, database storage and management, and direct marketing campaigns. We may share your Personal Information with these third parties, but only to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services. We also require these third parties to maintain the privacy and security of the Personal Information they process on our behalf. **Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement** Statusbrew cooperates with government and law enforcement officials or private parties to enforce and comply with the law. To the extent permitted under the applicable law, we may disclose any information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties as we believe is necessary or appropriate to investigate, respond to, and defend against claims, for legal process (including subpoenas), to protect the property and rights of Statusbrew or a third party, to protect Statusbrew against liability, for the safety of the public or any person, to prevent or stop any illegal, unethical, fraudulent, abusive, or legally actionable activity, to protect the security or integrity of the Service and any equipment used to make the Service available, or to comply with the law. **Business Transfers** Statusbrew may sell, transfer or otherwise share some or all of its assets, including Personal Information, in connection with a merger, acquisition, reorganization, sale of assets, or similar transaction, or in the event of insolvency or bankruptcy. You will have the opportunity to opt out of any such transfer if the new entity’s planned processing of your information differs materially from that set forth in this Privacy Policy. **Other Third Parties** We may share Personal Information with our headquarters and affiliates, and business partners to whom it is reasonably necessary or desirable for us to disclose your data for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. We may also make certain non-Personal Information available to third parties for various purposes, including for business or marketing purposes or to assist third parties in understanding our users’ interest, habits, and usage patterns for certain programs, content, services, advertisements, promotions, and functionality available through the Service.

#### 5\. HOW WE PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

Statusbrew is very concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your Personal Information. We employ administrative and electronic measures designed to appropriately protect your Personal Information against accidental or unlawful destruction, accidental loss, unauthorized alteration, unauthorized disclosure or access, misuse, and any other unlawful form of processing of the Personal Information in our possession. Please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. We cannot guarantee that information about you will not be accessed, viewed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our administrative, physical, and electronic safeguards, subject to requirements under applicable law to ensure or warrant information security. We will make any legally-required disclosures of any breach of the security, confidentiality, or integrity of your unencrypted electronically stored Personal Information to you via email or conspicuous posting on our Site in the most expedient time possible and without unreasonable delay, consistent with (i) the legitimate needs of law enforcement or (ii) any measures necessary to determine the scope of the breach and restore the reasonable integrity of the data system , and any other disclosures that may be required under applicable law. We also take measures to delete your Personal Information or keep it in a form that does not permit identifying you when this information is no longer necessary for the purposes for which we process it, unless we are required by law to keep this information for a longer period. When determining the retention period, we take into account various criteria, such as the type of products and services requested by or provided to you, the nature and length of our relationship with you, possible re-enrollment with our products or services, the impact on the services we provide to you if we delete some information from or about you, mandatory retention periods provided by law and the statute of limitations.

#### 6\. YOUR RIGHTS AND CHOICES

If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such marketing communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications. You may also opt out from receiving commercial email from us by sending your request to us by email at [privacy@statusbrew.com](mailto:privacy@statusbrew.com). Please be aware that, even after you opt out from receiving commercial messages from us, you will continue to receive administrative messages from us regarding the Service. In certain jurisdictions you have the right to request access and receive information about the Personal Information we maintain about you, to update and correct inaccuracies in your Personal Information, to restrict or object to the processing of your Personal Information, to have the information blocked, anonymized or deleted, as appropriate, or to exercise your right to data portability to transfer your Personal Information to another company. Those rights may be limited in some circumstances by local law requirements. In addition to the above-mentioned rights, you also have the right to lodge a complaint with a competent supervisory authority subject to applicable law. Where required by law, we obtain your consent for the processing of certain Personal Information collected by cookies or similar technologies, or used to send you direct marketing communications, or when we carry out other processing activities for which consent may be required. If we rely on consent for the processing of your Personal Information, you have the right to withdraw it at any time and free of charge. When you do so, this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before your consent withdrawal. To update your preferences, ask us to remove your information from our mailing lists, delete your account or submit a request to exercise your rights under applicable law, please contact us as specified in the “How to Contact Us” section below.

#### 7\. CAN-SPAM COMPLIANCE NOTICE (U.S. and Canadian users only)

We may send periodic promotional or informational emails to you. You may opt-out of such communications by following the unsubscribe or opt-out instructions contained in the email. Please note that it may take up to 10 business days for us to process opt-out requests. If you opt-out of receiving emails about recommendations or other information we think may interest you, we may still send you emails about your account or any Service you have requested or received from us.

#### 8\. CALIFORNIA PRIVACY RIGHTS

Pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, residents of California can obtain certain information about the types of Personally Identifiable Information that companies with whom they have an established business relationship have shared with third parties for direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. In particular, the law provides that companies must inform consumers about the categories of Personally Identifiable Information that have been shared with third parties, the names and addresses of those third parties, and examples of the types of services or products marketed by those third parties. To request a copy of the information disclosure provided by Statusbrew pursuant to Section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, please contact us via email at [privacy@statusbrew.com](mailto:privacy@statusbrew.com).

#### 9\. DATA TRANSFERS

Statusbrew is based in the United States. Personal Information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored at, any of our affiliates, partners or service providers which may be inside or outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”) and Switzerland, including the United States. By submitting your personal data, you agree to such transfers. Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries that do not have the same data protection laws as the country in which you initially provided the information. When we transfer or disclose your Personal Information to other countries, we will protect that information as described in this Privacy Policy.

##### 9.a If you are located in the European Economic Area ("EEA") or Switzerland

We will comply with applicable legal requirements for the transfer of Personal Information to countries outside of the EEA or Switzerland. In particular, Statusbrew has filed its certification of adherence to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the Department of Commerce and the European Commission, and the Swiss Federal Data Protection and Information Commissioner, respectively, with respect to the processing of certain Personal Information transferred from the EEA and Switzerland to Statusbrew. For additional details on our compliance with the EU-US privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss-US Privacy Shield Framework please visit <https://statusbrew.com/privacy-shield>. Statusbrew has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>. In addition, we may enter into Standard Contractual Clauses issued by the European Commission with our commercial customers where appropriate.

#### 10\. CHILDREN’S PRIVACY

The Site is not directed to persons under 16. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with Personal Information without their consent, he or she should contact us at [privacy@statusbrew.com](mailto:privacy@statusbrew.com). We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under 16. If we become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with Personal Information, we will delete such information from our files.

#### 11\. UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason; each version will apply to information collected while it was in place. We will notify you of any modifications to our Privacy Policy by posting the new Privacy Policy on our Site and indicating the date of the latest revision. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes. In the event that the modifications materially alter your rights or obligations hereunder, we will make reasonable efforts to notify you of the change. For example, we may send a message to your email address or generate a pop-up or similar notification when you access the Service for the first time after such material changes are made. Your continued use of the Service after the revised Privacy Policy has become effective indicates that you have read, understood and agreed to the current version of this Privacy Policy.

#### 12\. HOW TO CONTACT US

Chiax LLC (Statusbrew) is the entity responsible for the processing of your Personal Information. If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, or if you would like to exercise your rights to your Personal Information, you may contact us by emailing us at [privacy@statusbrew.com](mailto:privacy@statusbrew.com) or our [Web Contact Form](https://statusbrew.com/contact/general). This Privacy Policy is effective as of November 22, 2019. If you have any thoughts or questions about this Privacy Policy please contact us.
